<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>https://breachtactics.com/</id><title>BreachTactics</title><subtitle>Breach Tactics offers in-depth offensive security tutorials, red teaming strategies, and educational content for cybersecurity professionals to stay ahead of threats.</subtitle> <updated>2025-04-12T20:06:41-04:00</updated> <author> <name>breachtactics</name> <uri>https://breachtactics.com/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://breachtactics.com/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="https://breachtactics.com/"/> <rights> © 2025 breachtactics </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>Certified AI/ML Pentester Review</title><link href="https://breachtactics.com/blog/certified-ai-ml-pentester/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Certified AI/ML Pentester Review" /><published>2024-10-28T00:00:00-04:00</published> <updated>2024-10-28T00:00:00-04:00</updated> <id>https://breachtactics.com/blog/certified-ai-ml-pentester/</id> <content src="https://breachtactics.com/blog/certified-ai-ml-pentester/" /> <author> <name>breachtactics</name> </author> <category term="Education" /> <summary>As organizations race to adopt the latest in artificial intelligence (AI), I was looking for training that addressed its unique attack surface and tested my skills in exploiting large language models (LLM). That’s when I discovered The SecOps Group and their Certified AI/ML Pentester, which was one of the first certifications (I’ve seen*) to offer a practical exam on LLM exploitation. This pos...</summary> </entry> <entry><title>Active Directory ACL Abuse with Kali Linux</title><link href="https://breachtactics.com/blog/acl-abuse-with-kali/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Active Directory ACL Abuse with Kali Linux" /><published>2024-05-08T00:00:00-04:00</published> <updated>2024-05-08T00:00:00-04:00</updated> <id>https://breachtactics.com/blog/acl-abuse-with-kali/</id> <content src="https://breachtactics.com/blog/acl-abuse-with-kali/" /> <author> <name>breachtactics</name> </author> <category term="Windows" /> <summary>Active Directory Access Control Lists (ACL), and their associated Access Control Entries (ACE), define the entities and permissions of a specific AD object. If misconfigured, abusing these permissions can be an easy way of escalating privileges within an organization. Overview Many of the articles and guides demonstrating Active Directory ACL abuse showcase exploitation from a Windows host. F...</summary> </entry> <entry><title>Game Hacking: Hex Editing Save Files for Unlimited Cash</title><link href="https://breachtactics.com/blog/hex-editing-save-files/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Game Hacking: Hex Editing Save Files for Unlimited Cash" /><published>2023-08-10T00:00:00-04:00</published> <updated>2023-08-10T00:00:00-04:00</updated> <id>https://breachtactics.com/blog/hex-editing-save-files/</id> <content src="https://breachtactics.com/blog/hex-editing-save-files/" /> <author> <name>breachtactics</name> </author> <category term="Linux" /> <summary>After creating a Batocera live USB for retro gaming, I instantly started down the path of game hacking and researching how ROM’s (digital game copies) could be abused… This post serves as my introduction to video game hacking through analyzing two saved states of Pokemon Red and hex editing targeted values for unlimited cash! Getting Setup (Level 1) To start, I created a fresh Ubuntu virtual ...</summary> </entry> <entry><title>Decoding the Airwaves: Tracking Device Movements With WiFi</title><link href="https://breachtactics.com/blog/device-tracking-with-wifi/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Decoding the Airwaves: Tracking Device Movements With WiFi" /><published>2023-06-30T00:00:00-04:00</published> <updated>2023-06-30T00:00:00-04:00</updated> <id>https://breachtactics.com/blog/device-tracking-with-wifi/</id> <content src="https://breachtactics.com/blog/device-tracking-with-wifi/" /> <author> <name>breachtactics</name> </author> <category term="Wireless" /> <summary>One of the many rabbit holes Ive gone down recently was the use of WiFi to track client devices. While this technique is not new by any means, I recall seeing matt0177s 2022 Blackhat USA talk where he demonstrated using signal intelligence emitted from personal devices as a means of counter surveillance. This was the first practical application of device tracking I was exposed to and wanted to ...</summary> </entry> <entry><title>Portable Python for In-Memory Execution &amp; Modern Evasion</title><link href="https://breachtactics.com/blog/portable-python/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Portable Python for In-Memory Execution &amp;amp; Modern Evasion" /><published>2022-12-22T00:00:00-05:00</published> <updated>2022-12-22T00:00:00-05:00</updated> <id>https://breachtactics.com/blog/portable-python/</id> <content src="https://breachtactics.com/blog/portable-python/" /> <author> <name>breachtactics</name> </author> <category term="Windows" /> <summary>Forget compiling payloads and operating on disk — this post demonstrates the use of Python’s portable interpreter for in-memory malware deployment, even when the language isnt installed on the host. Why Python? Python is a well known language with an infinite number of legitimate uses inside an organization. Through the use of Python’s portable, or embedded package we can download a single .zi...</summary> </entry> </feed>
